One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Is Conis gonna be alright?
Conis'e bir şey olmaz umarım.
She wound up as an accomplice because she tried to save us!
Bizi kurtarmak istedi diye, adı suçluya çıktı!
She's gonna have hell to pay for sure!
Kesinlikle bunun cezasını çekecek!
That old Sky Knight said he'd look after her, but...
O yaşlı Gökyüzü Şövalyesi onunla ilgileneceğini söyledi ama...
Nah, he's weird, but I don't think he's a bad guy.
Evet, garip biri ama ondan bir zarar gelmez.
We don't have a choice.
Yapacak bir şey yok.
I wanna protect her, but we can't take her with us, either.
Ona göz kulak olmak istiyorum ama bizimle gelemezdi.
C'mon, this thing's so slow...
Bu da amma yavaşmış be...
Of course it is. It's way heavier than a waver.
Yavaş tabii, waver'a göre çok daha ağır bu.
Quit complaining!
Sızlanmayı kes!
Adventure on God's Island
Tanrı'nın Adasındaki Macera
Hey, look! What's with that humongous forest?!
Hey, bakın! Şu devasa orman da ne öyle?!
Is that Upper Yard?!
Yukarı Bahçe burası mı?!
Amazing! Was there a forest like this on the map?!
İnanılmaz! Haritada böyle bir orman var mıydı?
Well, the map did show a forest, but it was nothing like what's in front of us.
Harita bir orman gösteriyordu ama bu kadar büyük değildi!
This one's normal.
Gayet normal.
People from 200 years ago had that map, right?
O harita 200 yıl öncesinde kullanılıyordu, değil mi?
It might have been old even back then.
Belki de daha öncesine ait.
It'd take at least 1,000 years for trees to grow this massive!
Bu devasa ağaçlar en az 1000 yıllıktır!
That's true...
Doğru...
They sure are big trees!
Gerçekten devasalar!
I wanna climb 'em!
Tırmanasım geldi!
It's the entrance!
Giriş orada!
Well, if we're gonna turn back, now's our chance.
Geri dönmek istiyorsak bu son şansımız.
You ready, Usopp?
Hazır mısın, Usopp?
Huh? W-Well, I wouldn't mind if we went back–
Ha? Yani aslında geri dönsek fena olmazdı...
Let's go!
Hadi gidelim!
You weren't even gonna listen to me!
Lafı ağzıma tıktın!
I wanna go back...
Geri dönmek istiyorum...
Something's here!
Orada bir şey var!
Well, it is a forest!
Orman burası, olabilir!
Yeah, it is.
Evet, öyle.
N-N-No, just hold on! Look around you!
H-H-Hayır, öyle değil! Etrafınıza bakın!
It's nothing but shipwrecks!
Etrafımız gemi enkazlarıyla dolu!
It is a forest!
Orman işte!
Yeah, it is.
Evet, öyle.
How are those related?!
Ne alakası var?!
On top of that, they're all sliced in half...
Ayrıca hepsi ortadan ikiye bölünmüş...
Not again!
Yine mi?!
Like I said, forests are full of all sorts of–
Dediğim gibi, ormanlar–
I was wrong!
Yanılmışım!
Hurry, full speed ahead! Hurry! Paddle, paddle! Go!
Çabuk, tam yol ileri! Acele edin! Kürek çek, kürek!
Huh? What's going on?
Ha? Ne oluyor?
A sickle monster!
Orak canavarı!
Watch out! There's another one!
Dikkat edin! Başka bir tane geliyor!
No... Not just one...!
Hayır... Sadece bir tane değil...!
Paddle like hell!
Asılın lan küreklere!
What's trying to kill us now?!
Bu ne böyle be?!
Luffy, pay attention! Hit the brake!
Luffy, dikkat et! Frene bas!
We're not gonna make it! Take the wheel, Usopp!
Başaramayacağız! Dümeni al, Usopp!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Luffy, what're you doing?! Eyes forward!
Luffy, ne yapıyorsun?! Ters yöndesin!
Just keep going straight!
Sen düz devam et!
...Bazooka!
...Bazuka!
Dodged it!
Kaçabildik!
That was close!
Çok yakındı!
We managed to evade it...
Paçayı kurtardık...
but it's not looking good! We can't go back now!
Ama artık geri dönemeyiz!
We've come a long way from the entrance!
Girişi geçeli çok oldu!
Wanna get off here?
Sen in istersen?
Don't be stupid! I'd die!
Aptal mısın?! Ölür giderim!
Yeah, probably.
Evet, muhtemelen.
What was that, a snake?!
O neydi öyle, yılan mıydı?!
A lamprey. So, a sky lamprey, I guess?
Taşemen. Muhtemelen gökyüzü taşemeni diyorlar.
One that big will do more than suck a little blood!
Bu kadar büyüğü kan emmekten fazlasını yapar!
What a neat forest!
On numara ormanmış he!
Neat, my butt! If this is our ordeal, I've already had enough!
Kıçımın on numarası! Testimiz buysa bana yetti bile!
But we've only just entered the forest.
Ama daha ormana yeni girdik.
We'll really be screwed if we stall or stop on this milky road...
Bu kanalda oyalanırsak başımız dertten kurtulmaz...
Looks like our only choice is to keep moving!
Tek seçeneğimiz ilerlemek!
There he is!
İşte orada!
Zoro!
Zoro!
He's gonna lose to the sky shark!
Gökyüzü köpek balığı, onu yiyecek!
He went under again...
Yine battı...
Zoro isn't coming back up!
Yukarı çıkmıyor!
Do you think... he got eaten?!
Sizce... balıklara yem mi oldu?!
Zoro was eaten!
Zoro'yu yediler!
If he were eaten, the clouds would turn red.
Yenmiş olsaydı bulutlar kıpkırmızı olurdu.
Don't say such ominous things with a straight face, Robin!
Böyle korkunç şeyleri sakin bir suratla söyleme, Robin!
You're finished!
Yettin ulan!
This is bad...
Durum hiç iyi değil...
Looks like swimming away is out of the question.
Buradan yüzerek kaçmak iyi bir fikir değil!
Why'd you punch it?! I thought you were a swordsman.
Niye yumruk attın?! Sen kılıç ustası değil misin?
Zoro's so strong!
Zoro çok güçlü!
I'm certain that this is the interior of Upper Yard.
Buranın Yukarı Bahçe'nin iç kısmı olduğuna eminim.
It's almost as if this is a sacrificial altar...
Bu sunak, sanki birilerini kurban etmek için yapılmış gibi...
Now there's a giant!
Şimdi de ileride bir dev var!
No. That's a statue!
Hayır. O bir heykel!
Hey, but... it's totally a dead end.
Ama burası çıkmaz bir yol gibi duruyor...
No, there are four entrances!
Hayır, dört farklı giriş var!
And let me guess; each one leads to a different place.
Dur tahmin edeyim; hepsi farklı bir yere gidiyor.
"Ordeal of Swamp."
"Bataklık Testi"
"Ordeal of Iron."
"Demir Testi"
"Ordeal of String."
"İp Testi"
"Ordeal of Balls."
"Top Testi"
Can we go in any one of them?!
İstediğimize girebiliyor muyuz?
Is "God" trying to play games with us or something?
Bu "Tanrı" bizimle oyun mu oynuyor?
Four ordeals... Which one do we choose?
Dört test... Hangisini seçeceğiz?
A second-degree crime, huh? Does God mean nothing to them?!
İkinci derece suç, ha? Tanrı'nın onlar için hiçbir anlamı yok mu?!
Go ahead... Choose. We'll gladly indulge you in any of them.
Seçin birini... İstediğinizi size seve seve sunacağız.
It's a sin to live in ignorance.
Cehalet içinde yaşamak günahtır.
The means to attaining peace do not lead one to heaven.
Barışı sağlamaya niyetlenmek cennete gitmeyi garantilemez.
Swamp!
Bataklık!
Iron!
Demir!
String!
İp!
Balls!
Top!
Choose an ordeal!
Seçin birini!
So what do we choose?
Hangisini seçeceğiz?
Alright! Let's go with "Balls"!
Pekâlâ! Top'u seçelim!
Why's that, Luffy?
Neden, Luffy?
Because balls are fun!
Kulağa eğlenceli geliyor!
That's your reason?!
Bu mu sebep?!
These are ordeals! They're not gonna be fun!
Test edileceğiz! Hiçbiri eğlenceli olmayacak!
But I do agree with "Balls."
Ama Top'u seçmek konusunda katılıyorum.
It's the ordeal that sounds the least violent.
Kulağa en az şiddetli o geliyor...
Then it's decided. But don't let your guard down.
O zaman karar verildi. Ama dikkatli olun.
We're on God's Island, 10,000 meters in the sky!
Yerden 10,000 metre yüksekte, Tanrı'nın adasındayız!
Anything could happen here!
Burada ne olacağını bilemeyiz!
Let's go! Balls!
Hadi gidelim! Top!
Hey, helmsman! Might wanna keep your eyes open!
Hey, dümenci! Gözlerini açık tutsan iyi olur!
Open or closed, it's still pitch black!
Gözümü açsam bile zifiri karanlık!
Hey, is there other stuff like this?
Hey, diğerleri de aynı mıydı?
Like what?
Ne gibi?
So with only four entrances...
Dört farklı giriş vardı ya,
what if only one of them was the lucky one?!
belki de bir tanesi güvenli, diğerleri tehlikeliydi.
Huh?! Don't say that kind of crap now!
Ha?! Ağzını hayra aç lan!
What happens if we chose the wrong one?!
Ya tehlikeli olanı seçtiysek?!
If it's the wrong one? Hmm...
Ya bu tehlikeli olansa? Hmm...
Maybe we'll fall off the sky island?
Belki Gökyüzü Adası'ndan düşeriz.
We can't afford to fall off!
Aptal aptal konuşma, düşersek ölürüz be!
It's 10,000 meters to the Blue Sea, you know!
Mavi Deniz, 10,000 metre aşağıda!
This high up, 1,000 lives would flash before your eyes!
Bu yükseklik, insanın ömründen bin ömür götürür!
It's too crazy to even think about!
Düşünmesi bile korkunç!
Quit being dumbasses! That's obviously not gonna hap–
Salak salak konuşmayın! Öyle bir şey olmaya–
No way! You have got to be kidding me!
Olamaz! Şaka mı bu?!
It wasn't just one! There's a whole swarm of sky sharks!
Yalnızca bir tane yokmuş! Bir sürü köpek balığı var!
We'd be here until nightfall if we fought every one of them.
Her biriyle dövüşmeye kalkarsak bütün gece buradayız demektir.
We'd never reach shore at that rate...
Kıyıya da mümkün değil ulaşamayız.
But we can't just sit here, either.
Burada bir şey yapmadan oturacak hâlimiz de yok.
That giant lobster brought us to one hell of a place...
O dev ıstakoz bizi ne biçim bir yere getirdiyse...
Do you suppose starving us here is "Divine Reckoning"?
Acaba bizi burada açlığa terk etmeleri "İlahi Adalet" dedikleri şey mi?
Would a god really do something so tasteless?
Tanrı dedikleri böyle yavan bir cezayı mı uygun görür sence?
Hard to say. I've never met one.
Bilmiyorum. Daha önce hiç bir tanrı ile tanışmadım.
This is bad...
Durum berbat...
We can't set the boat in the water with the hull like this.
Teknenin gövdesi böyle zarar görmüşken yelken açamayız.
Try to fix the ship somehow, Chopper.
Gemiye bir şekilde tamir et, Chopper.
Huh? Me?! Okay...
Ha? Ben mi?! Tamam...
Fix it? What are you up to?
Tamir mi? Ne planlıyorsun?
I've gotta get into this forest.
Ormanın içine girmeliyim.
For now, let's make this our base of operations.
Şimdilik burayı üs belleyelim.
I'm sure Luffy and the others are headed here to search for us.
Eminim Luffy ve diğerleri de bizi arıyorlardır.
It's like they say, "If you get lost, stay put."
Hani derler ya, "Kaybolduysan, olduğun yerde kal".
You need to stay put the most!
Diyene bak be!
Say, Zoro... you said you're going into the forest, but what for?
Baksana Zoro... Ormana gireceğim dedin, neden ki?
There's a god on this island, right? I'm gonna go meet him.
Bu adada bir Tanrı var, değil mi? Gidip tanışacağım.
I'm telling you, that's a bad idea! What if you run into those freaks?!
Bu hiç iyi bir fikir değil! Ya o garip tiplere denk gelirsen?!
Good question. I guess it all depends on how they act.
O zaman onların tavrına göre ne yapacağım değişir.
Zoro... it's like you're mightier than a god...
Zoro... Tanrı'dan bile kudretli duruyorsun.
He has priests on this island too, you know!
Burada rahipleri de var, biliyorsun değil mi?!
We can't make a god angry! It's common sense, you know!
Bu tanrıyı kızdıramayız! Biraz sağduyun olsun!
Sorry, but...
Üzgünüm ama...
I've never once prayed to a god.
hayatımda hiçbir tanrıya el açmadım.
So cool!
Ne kadar havalı!
I don't believe in them either, so I don't owe this god a thing.
Hem bu tanrıya inanmıyorum, yani ona bir şey borçlu değilim.
Oh, mighty God!
Ah, yüce Tanrı'm!
I have nothing to do with him! Please don't punish me!
Bu adamı tanımıyorum! Lütfen beni cezalandırma!
That vine looks usable.
Şu sarmaşığı kullanabilirim.
You're right, good idea.
Haklısın, iyi fikir.
Mind if I join you, Mr. Swordsman?
Sana katılabilir miyim, bay Kılıç Ustası?
Huh? Sure, but don't go slowing me down!
Ha? Olur ama beni yavaşlatma!
Hold on!
Bekle!
Where are you going, Robin?!
Sen nereye gidiyorsun, Robin?!
Look at this.
Şuna bakın.
This altar was built at least 1,000 years ago.
Bu sunak, 1000 yılı aşkın bir süre önce yapılmış.
– At least... 1,000 years?!
– 1000 yıl mı?!
Historical findings like this make me prickle with excitement!
Böyle tarihi şeylere bayılırım!
Where there is a rich history, there will be an abundance of relics.
Böyle eski yerlerde çokça tarihi eser de olur.
Perhaps even a few jewels that would help pay for ship repairs.
Belki geminin tamir masrafları için biraz mücevher bile buluruz.
I'm coming too!
Ben de geliyorum!
Really?! Even after you were so scared?!
Ne?! Hani korkuyordun?!
It's for investigating history!
Tarihi araştırıyoruz!
Those are belly signs...
Gözleri beli'ye döndü...
Do you have to make that sound?
O sesi yapmak zorunda mıydın?
Robin is amazing!
Robin inanılmazsın!
She did it so easily...
Ne kadar kolay yaptı...
This might be a bit too high up...
Sanki biraz fazla yüksekteyim...
It's about fifty meters! If you slip, you'll die!
Aşağı yukarı 50 metre! Düşersen ölürsün!
Stop saying morbid things!
Korkunç şeyler söylemesene!
I really am a goner if I fall!
Düşersem işim biter!
Nami...
Nami...
T-Too fast! I can't stop!
Ç-Çok hızlı! Duramayacağım!
See? You have courage.
Bak. Cesaretin varmış.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Zahmet verdim, kusura bakma.
Not at all.
Önemli değil.
That's because you didn't go, "Aah-eeh-ah-eeh-aaaaaah!"
"Aaa-aaaaa-aaaaa!" diye bağırmadın ondan olmadı.
Is that the issue here?!
Sorun o muydu sence?!
This certainly is a big forest...
Gerçekten devasa bir orman...
Okay, Chopper! You're in charge of the ship!
Pekâlâ, Chopper! Gemi sana emanet!
You've got this!
Sana güveniyoruz!
We'll be back soon!
Yakında döneriz!
Right! Be careful, everyone! Come back safe!
Tamam! Dikkatli olun! Kendinize dikkat edin!
I guess Nami will be okay since she has Zoro and Robin.
Nami, yanında Robin ve Zoro varken iyi olacaktır.
I'm too scared to go...
Ben gitmeye çok korktum...
Everyone is so brave and amazing!
Herkes ne kadar cesur ve havalı!
I wonder if I'll be brave someday, too...
Acaba bir gün, ben de bu kadar cesur olabilecek miyim...?
Anyway, I'll do everything I can now!
Neyse, şimdi elimden geleni yapmalıyım!
Taking care of the ship by myself in a dangerous forest
Yalnız başıma bu tehlikeli ormanda gemi bana emanet!
is proof that everyone has faith in me!
Yani herkes bana güveniyor!
I gotta do my best!
Var gücümle denemeliyim!
That's right! I'm all alone in this dangerous place–
Evet! Bu tehlikeli yerde tek başımayı–
I'm the one in the most danger!
Asıl tehlikede olan benim!
We're alive...
Hayattayız...
I seriously thought we were gonna fall 10,000 meters...
Cidden 10,000 metreden düşüyoruz sandım...
You freaked Usopp out with that nonsense, Luffy!
Usopp'u saçmalıklarınla sen korkuttun, Luffy!
That was scary! I thought I was gonna die!
Çok korkunçtu! Öleceğim sandım!
But still, what is this place?
O değil de burası ne böyle?
They're balls. Definitely balls.
Toplar var. Bunlar top kesin.
They're little balls of island cloud...
Top şeklinde ada bulutları bunlar...
Awesome! They're like big snow!
Harika! Koca kartopları gibiler!
What a weird place! It's so neat!
Ne garip bir yer! Çok iyi!
The milky road leads above the trees...
Yol, ağaçların tepesine doğru çıkıyor...
But what part of this is an ordeal?
Ama burada test, tam olarak ne?
Who knows?
Kim bilir?
It'd be great if there's nothing at all, but I doubt that's the case.
Test falan olmasaydı iyi olurdu ama öyle olacağını sanmıyorum.
Maybe we did get the lucky entrance!
Belki de doğru kapıyı seçtik!
I bet if we chose one of the others, we'd be in trouble right about now!
Eminim ki diğer kapıları seçseydik şu an hepimiz hapı yutmuştuk!
Y-Yeah! You might be right!
E-Evet! Haklı olabilirsin!
Right?!
Değil mi?!
You idiots, don't let your guard down!
Aptallar, gardınızı düşürmeyin!
Would they really let criminals off without a hitch?
Suçlulara bir şey yapmadan bırakırlar mı sizce?
Think about it!
Biraz mantıklı düşünün!
There might be traps like earlier...
Az önceki gibi tuzaklar olabilir...
Stay alert!
Gözünüzü dört açın!
Let's just keep moving...
Şimdilik ilerlemeye devam edelim...
I'm thirsty! Let's have some tea!
Susadım! Bir çay içelim!
Huh? Yeah, let's! Open the rice crackers in your bag!
Ha? Evet, içelim! Şu çantadaki pirinç krakerlerinden de versene!
Oh, good idea!
Ah, güzel fikir!
You sons of...
Ulan ben sizin...
C'mon, just one rice cracker!
Hadi ama alt tarafı bir kraker!
Yeah! Let's eat, let's eat!
Evet! Hadi yiyelim!
Knock it off! Listen, I'm gonna keep steering.
Kesin be! Dinleyin, ben dümendeyim.
You guys keep watch on both sides!
Siz de yan taraflardan gözcülük yapın!
It took us really high up at some point...
Daha da yükseğe çıkıyoruz...
But it's strange...
Ama çok garip...
There are four priests, so I assumed each entrance would lead us to one...
Dört rahip olduğu için her bir giriş bizi bir rahibe götürecek sandım,
but I guess not.
ama yanıldım galiba.
Hey, Usopp! Pass!
Hey, Usopp! Pas!
Okay! I got it! Pass!
Tamam! Karşıladım! Pas!
I told you to keep watch!
Size gözcülük yapın dedim be!
A snake!
Yılan!
You jerk! Beat it!
Şerefsiz seni! Defol!
That was a surprise! Why would...?
Sürpriz oldu! Ha...?
Sanji! Look out! There's another cloud!
Sanji! Bak! Başka bir bulut!
Kick it far away!
Tekmele gitsin!
Dammit! Are all these floating things snake eggs?!
Kahretsin! Bunlar yılan yumurtası mı?!
– This isn't good...
– Boku yedik...
What's the deal with these balls?!
Bu topların olayı ne lan?!
There's no telling what's inside!
İçlerinde ne olduğunu bilmenin bir yolu yok!
These clouds are called surprise clouds!
Onlar sürpriz bulutları!
Surprise clouds?!
Sürpriz bulutları mı?!
Heso!
Heso!
Who's there?!
Sen kimsin?!
Thank you for choosing my Ordeal of Balls!
Top Testi'mi seçtiğiniz için teşekkür ederim!
Satori of the Forest Skypiea Priest
Orman Satori Skypiea Rahibi
What's with the dumpling freak?
Kim bu toparlak ucube?
Don't tell me he's a priest?!
Rahiplerden biri mi yoksa?!
You're the ball in the Ordeal of Balls?!
Top Sınavı'ndaki top sen misin?!
Quit dancing around! Who the hell are you?!
Kes lan dans etmeyi! Kimsin lan?!
Wow, he seems dumber than I expected...
Tam bir aptala benziyor...
Didn't Nami and the old guy say they were really strong?
Nami ve ihtiyar, bunlar çok güçlü dememiş miydi?
Hey! Dumpling!
Hey! Toparlak!
Nami's group had better be safe!
Nami-san ve diğerleri güvendedir umarım!
You mean the sacrifices?
Adakları mı diyorsun?
If so, I wouldn't know! But they'll die if they're left alone!
Öyleyse, bilmiyorum! Ama yalnız kalırlarsa ölecekler!
And even if they escape, they're still going to die!
Kaçarlarsa da ölecekler!
Say what?!
Ne dedin sen?!
You should worry about yourselves.
Kendiniz için endişelenin.
In case you didn't realize it, you'll need to defeat me to continue ahead!
Hâlâ anlamadıysanız, devam etmeniz için beni yenmeniz gerekiyor!
Okay, Luffy! Here he comes! Get 'im!
Tamam, Luffy! İşte geliyor! Bitir işini!
Alright! I'll knock him out of the air!
Pekâlâ! Onu indireceğim!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Oh, you're going to stretch?
Ah, esneyecek misin?
...Pistol!
...Tabanca!
No way!
Olamaz!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy?! Hey! You're okay, right?!
Luffy?! Hey! İyi misin?!
A regular hit shouldn't affect you!
Sıradan bir darbenin sana işlememesi gerekirdi!
A regular hit?
Sıradan bir darbe mi?
This is a bit different from a regular hit!
Bu sıradan bir darbeden biraz farklı!
The hell do you mean by that?!
Gösteririm sana farklıyı!
An upward kick with the right leg...
Sağ bacakla yukarı doğru tekme...
Collier– What?!
Collier– Ne?!
Those with enough discipline and training are given the power of mantra.
Yeterli disipline ve eğitime sahip olanlara "Mantra" gücü bahşedilir.
Impossible! He predicted my movements?!
İmkânsız! Hareketimi önceden sezdi mi?!
Sanji!
Sanji!
It is different from a hit!
Normal bir darbeden farklı!
Impact!
Darbe!
The shock destroys the body from the inside!
Şok darbesi, vücudu içeriden parçalar!
D-Dammit! Sanji! Usopp!
K-Kahretsin! Sanji! Usopp!
Yeah, I'm alright... But what the hell was that?!
Ben iyiyim... Ama o neydi öyle be?!
No idea at all...! He's a mystery!
Hiçbir fikrim yok...! Esrarengiz bir tip!
My name is Satori!
Benim adım, Satori!
I am one of the priests of the almighty God Enel!
Yüce Tanrı Enel'in rahiplerinden biriyim!
I own the vearth in these Lost Woods.
Bu Kayıp Orman'daki vearth'ın sahibi benim.
Lost Woods?
Kayıp Orman mı?
Yes!
Evet!
That is what we call this forest!
Bu ormanın ismi budur!
And...
Ve...
your boat will be lost within it!
botunuz içinde kaybolacak!
The boat is taking off!
Bot gidiyor!
Your boat will now speed along the milky road at random
Botunuz ormanda rastgele dolaşacak artık...
and eventually leave through this forest's only exit!
ve sonunda bu ormanın tek çıkışından ayrılacak!
I'm sure you realize it, but losing a dial boat
Farkında mısınız bilmiyorum ama botunuzu kaybetmek,
is the same as losing your way to the sacrificial altar.
sunağa gitme şansınızı da kaybetmeniz anlamına geliyor.
So you must find and board the boat before that happens.
Yani botunuzu bulmanız gerekiyor.
Of course, these countless surprise clouds and I will not allow that.
Ve tabii ki sayısız sürpriz bulutları ve ben, buna müsaade etmeyeceğiz.
Welcome to the sacred ground of Upper Yard!
Kutsal yer, Yukarı Bahçe'ye hoş geldiniz!
This is the Lost Woods' Ordeal of Balls, which has a 10 percent survival rate!
İşte, Kayıp Orman'ın %10 hayatta kalma oranına sahip "Top Testi"!
A 10 percent survival rate?!
%10 hayatta kalma oranı mı?!